what's the most fun you've ever had with
me and why I think on Halloween when we
went to the stacks and it was just like
I was so drunk but I was so I don't
think I hadn't known you that long
I mean I'd known you but I think it was
the first time I felt like I could just
like be crazy around you because I had
felt so subdued around you before and I
even said something like I don't feel
like I've shown you everything at this
point I think I said something before
Halloween happened and then it started
ringing and we ran around in the rain
and we had like kissing in the rain and
dancing yeah it was pouring so much fun
what's your first impression of me um my
first impression of you hmm I don't know
you're really sweet I thought you were
very courteous because you laughed at
all my really bad jokes and that was
really nice cuz I was really nervous yes
when I first met you and and yeah that
just made me feel comfortable yeah I
don't know your s just somebody who
there's somebody who could be a friend I
guess a friend
yeah just like because you were just so
genuine I think I think genuine is a
good word you know I didn't feel like
you were trying to be somebody else yes
cool that make sense
yeah what's the most ridiculous thing
I've done what did it teach you about me
okay well we went to see after we went
to see that opera show that I didn't
like and you liked and first of all
you're seeing opera in the car
and then that was ridiculous but we went
to get fun and you got up in the middle
of the restaurant and because we were
having a conversation about how I can't
like my memory is pretty bad and you're
like well you should like make things
more memorable like you should I don't
know I don't I don't know what you were
trying to do but you got up and started
dancing but it looked like flailing to
me and everybody was like looking and it
was it was absolutely ridiculous I don't
remembered it I remembered it although
there was at one time in the car you
couldn't oh yeah no there was that
moment you didn't like that
well I feel like I failed oh no I knew
when do you feel closest to me um I
think I feel closest to you when well go
with the more obvious answer and then
I'll try to think of something more
interesting when we're like in bed
together
and our faces are like so close together
that we can't even focus our eyes but we
just like stay that way anyways I think
I don't know I'm just just something
about being our faces being that close
together it's like it's really special
and nice or when we're dancing yeah yeah
I just that's really nice and
I think those moments are really special
it's my dream two-part question
what do I do that turns you on and when
do you feel most sexy with me okay you
do a lot of silly things without weirdly
turn me on like when you speak in that
southern accent that's so southern that
you can't really distinguish what you're
saying it's I don't know why it's so
sexy to me it's like so it's just maybe
the fact that you can just make fun of
yourself and be silly like that boy yeah
yeah it's a Texan in music yeah and I
feel most sexy when you tell me I am
that's what I feel most sexy really yeah
if you could wish one thing for me what
would it be and why um I would wish that
that you find like the the thing that
gives you like a lot of fulfillment
you know because you will you know move
to New York to be on Broadway and then
realize you didn't want to be on
Broadway and and I think now that now
you're like in school and trying to
figure out what it is you know and it
doesn't have to be professionally you
know but just just something that like
really gives you fulfillment yeah
something that you love to do and you
can do everyday
okay breathe breathing through them
what are you hesitant to tell me
[Music]
oh I wrote it actually in one of the
letters I gave you for Valentine's Day
that you and you haven't opened yet
obviously
mm-hmm as a kind of like as an incentive
for me to tell you because I want to but
I don't want you to feel like it's
pressure or like you have to say
something to me
in return but I think that I've never I
think you know what I'm trying to say I
don't you know I think you know I don't
want to say it but if you know because
I'm really scared to say this okay and
you know what I'm okay
yeah and yeah I am too mmm and I think
that yeah I don't I've never I've never
told any of my partners people that have
had a relationship with and yeah I've
never told told anyone that I've that I
love them and in some ways that like was
a big reason why my last relationship
ended and yeah I think that that's
that's just something like there's
something to that word when in in like
that context that has so much weight for
me yeah and and it's such a special
thing so I very like I think I'm very
sensitive and very cautious
with how I use it but I also think that
I'm probably too cautious because I
don't know like when you care about
somebody and and they're an important
part of your life and then like they
deserve that you know they deserve to be
told that and yeah I think it just has
something to do with maybe the way I was
raised you know like in a very sort of
conservative family who I think they
play like a lot of emphasis on love and
romance that's like very serious and but
I don't know like it's I think it's
something that's everyone's very strange
for me you you think you've never been
in love before or you know you haven't
never been no I don't know I think I
think and I think in a lot of ways I
have you know and I think that I
experience different kinds of love yeah
you know you know obviously like love
for your friends I think is very
different yeah can I say I love you to
my friends all the time yeah but I think
there's something like with them yeah
there's more there's more wait yeah but
I know what do you I just think like I'm
just so hesitant because it's only been
I've only known you for six months maybe
a little more than that and it's weird
for me because I'm like I don't this
doesn't happen to me very easily that I
even like someone really like and want
to go past like four days and I just
maybe it's not and maybe it's not love
like yet or whatever but I just it's
something that I'm feeling that I
haven't like it's just an intense
feeling that I have and that's the what
comes to my tongue when I see you when I
say goodbye to you when I like I don't
know when we're laying in bed next to
each other like it comes to my like it
comes to the back of my teeth
and then don't say it because I don't
know it's the same thing for me I'm
hesitant it makes it's very important to
me that I mean it and it's very
important to me that the person who says
it to me means it and I think that's why
I haven't said it to you because I know
like I feel so strongly like I mean it
but I just want to be sure but I don't
know if like you're saying like how do
you really how can you be like so sure
so positive I want to be so positive and
I think really what I need to be
positive about it is to know that it's
reciprocated but I don't that's why I
preface this by saying I don't want the
pressure you know
so it's looming you know no I believe
like I've definitely it's it's been
there for me too and yeah I guess I just
don't know it's just really hard I think
for me cuz I don't know I just don't
know where like I stand and it's sort of
my I don't know I just feel like there's
so much and I feel like we still are
like a really it's a really new
relationship and and I still feel like I
have so much to learn but like I'm I
don't know what I want to do with my
life
like I don't I just feel almost stupid
like feeling the way that I'm feeling
because it's like so far past where I
feel like I should be yeah I don't want
to talk about this anymore
yeah I mean I let's do something to say
yeah I just I don't know I feel like so
much of my life has been just being
hesitant or nervous about saying that to
somebody else and part of me I'm just
torn because part of me feels like that
like yes you should hold that word too
like there that phrase to the highest
standard and like and and I think I do
like I but then part of me feels like
you know like you know you should just
let your heart be open to whatever you
know and not think so much I think I
just think too much about it and about
everything I could just just churning
all the time and and I don't know so I
just yeah I just I'm like constantly in
this back and forth I'm just like no bu
like you really care about this person
like show you know show that through
words you know like you can do that and
then and then part of me feels like you
just don't rush into anything whatever
it's like it's weird because I get a lot
of pressure from this is so weird this
is such a weird kind of pressure to put
on somebody but from Jordan because when
he met you and then he saw us together
he was like oh my god you're in love
with him you're so in love with it I
mean he's so in love with you and I was
just like shut up shut up because like I
had already been thinking about it and
for somebody on the outside to say that
they saw something like that was I don't
know kind of pushed me forward a little
bit maybe I shouldn't have let it but
you know I really I trust him and he
knows me very well so I don't know okay
I'm gonna ask you a question oh okay
yeah okay what do you think is the
biggest challenge to our relationship
well I think well I think this is one
yeah yeah just kind of trying to
understand where we're both at you know
romantic feelings towards each other you
know like and they're just just cuz I
know we both care about each other
deeply you know but just I don't know I
guess they look like yeah the love thing
like trying to figure it out
I don't know I think I have
apprehensions about it and I think
that's a challenge and then just I mean
you know we've talked about it
I don't know where I'm gonna be in you
know a month or two months or a year or
whatever and you you could be moving to
the bay and you know a couple months you
know which is a challenge I think just
because you know who knows what's gonna
happen but I feel like I don't I feel
like we're in a good place I feel like
we're both we're both enjoying the
moment in a lot of ways like just that's
another reason I don't want to say like
I didn't want to say that because I just
want to enjoy it with you because I
don't know where you know I don't know
where I'm gonna go just go on I don't
know if I'm gonna move and you don't
know where you're gonna be and it's like
I just want to enjoy it and I don't want
that but I also just want you to know
like I want you to know so bad well now
I do know you know I think about it
that's how you know yeah and I do too
okay
and yeah I don't know like when it's but
I care about you deeply
and you know like I do love you
are you just saying now no I don't think
so I think but I mean I'm saying that
with maybe the just like I don't really
know what that means fully but but if
I'm gonna like define it for me right
now in my life which is like you have
somebody that you care about that you
enjoy spending time with that you feel
like you're learning from and growing
with then then yeah I do you know yeah
and but I don't I mean to be honest I
don't know like how that can change or
what's gonna happen but I think part of
what I like about us is that we just
kind of go with it you know like we
don't really know and I think we should
just keep doing that and then like they
said that but I don't want you to think
that now I expect I'm saying it to me it
was not guilty no I know I know I don't
think that you would say it if you
didn't want to say it but I also don't
want you to feel like you know now it's
a thing that we have said I hate that
it's like a milestone okay you know wow
I feel good yeah yeah cool okay I feel
good
okay no it's yours oh it's mine yeah mmm
am I the best sex you've ever had
yes you are mine very much so what do
you think is the hardest thing for me
right now the hardest thing for you yeah
I mean I guess and maybe you can say
what you think but I've just that kind
of figuring out yeah school major career
life you know where you gonna live yes
everything
yeah you think that's you got it what
can I do to improve our relationship
nothing I want you to do what you do
because I want to look good no I just
want to experience it the way that you
want it to be you know I like I don't
want you to I don't think that I have an
answer to that really I don't think that
there's anything that I think is not
good right now hmm other than like
what's gonna happen later but nobody can
do anything about that anyway mm-hmm
nothing okay wait you have to look at my
eyes right no I answered it all right is
it mine no I think it's mine
didn't you just yeah yeah that's you
do you believe in the one and am i it
what makes you believe in the one I
don't believe in the one I believe
there's so many ones that it all just
comes down to circumstances and the
right time right place you know if I was
having a really bad day and I felt like
crap and I probably might have had a bad
date and we even never be sitting here
you know but I was probably having a
pretty good day and I was excited and I
don't know it's great to meet you and
everything was great
and then so I mean yeah I don't know I
guess that's right yeah
then there's only one yeah and also
statistically very yeah when do you
think I take you for granted and why I
don't think I just simply do not think
that like I hate that I'm like you're a
great--you're I don't know like I hurt
yeah right trust me I want to answer
that but I don't maybe when I like make
a plan like that I'm excited about we
talked about this recently when I make a
plan that I'm excited about you know and
you kind of just want to invite people
but it's just out of like oh I missed
that dude Michael like let's invite him
- Oh what miss Ben was inviting it's
like you just want you just love
everyone and you just want to hang out
with everyone at the same time but
sometimes I just want like time with you
but I don't know that that's necessarily
taken but your deaths you've taken me
for granted
maybe it's just like not recognizing
what I want
what do you wish I did differently you
know something I just had a conversation
with a friend recently we were talking
about you know texting verse calling and
I feel like we text a lot more than we
talk to each other in the phone yeah I
hate that so I guess yeah it'd be nice
if unless it's you know you know making
plans or like meet up here or here's the
address you know it'd be nice just to
talk and hear your voice and yeah
instead of texting I feel like I feel
like a relationships maybe a little too
text heavy yeah but you've actually
tried to do recently I noticed that yeah
I don't like just texting anyway yeah
yeah you're always like throwing your
phone can't do this right now
yeah that's good what do you think is
the most important lesson I'm learning
at this stage in my life
what yep living I think something over
here here okay okay I think
maybe this is like I'm going to twist
this a little bit I think maybe this is
just how I see you but I sometimes just
think that you aren't realistic about
things like just it's the simplest thing
that you're just not realistic about
like when you told me about three
bottles of honey this is tiny but I was
like why do you really bought three
bottles just so many that's just a small
example but like in the giant bag of
can't like I don't know you can all
before it goes bad okay for myself okay
I don't know it's like like I just think
they're sweet so it's how is it the most
important lesson well I'm getting OH
so but I think like sometimes I'll seeds
like take a step back I just wish I had
a better example than pickles on honey
but you know you like it a step back and
you like Oh Bobby that was like oh I
should have thought about that or
whatever I just think like there are
some circumstances especially for me
because I'm a planner when it comes to
planning you know like but I think that
I always see you do that and I always
want to just be like what why though
like what it was like didn't you think
about just because that's the way that I
think like I just plan and you I don't
think you really plan that much I don't
know but I think I always see like you
know the calculation right in your head
like another example because I see I see
buying three jars of honey is like
planning for the future I'm always gonna
go bad but the kale I was just like
a lot it's for lunches at work okay
see Wow okay that's fine no oh no I I
think I know which we how about when we
went hiking with my brother Drake and
you were like and we were all so dirty
and sweaty and covered in sunscreen and
you were like oh let's go visit Jacob
and his house if he's here and I was
just like I'm so tired
like I know do you really want to go to
sit in someone's living room right now
with my brother who's 18 like I don't
know okay yeah I twisted that a little
bit maybe it's not a lesson movie it's
just something that I want to just why
haven't you given up on our relationship
Oh cuz I like you and I like spending
time with you and and it's like I don't
know I think like you're a really
wonderful person and I feel like I'm
learning a lot like how my lack of
planning yeah and it's just it's just
nice to have you around and to hold you
and
yeah well yeah like I don't know that
the idea giving up on the relationship
they did seem so far from how has your
parents relationship influenced our
relationship I just think a lot of
people think that my like having
divorced parents is like the worst thing
ever but for me I think it happened at a
time where I could understand it because
I was a senior in high school and I'm
you know I it was miserable to be in a
house with them and okay I can answer
this it was miserable
to be in a house with them because they
were always yelling and fighting and it
was one parent against the other and
like that there was just no cohesiveness
and the house at all and when they moved
out they became great friends and I
think it just showed me what I what I
don't want that like you can have like
you can find a partner that you're great
friends with but that's not like enough
you have to kind of just be on the same
same wavelength
and I just want to be on the same
wavelength as somebody I want them to
you know obviously that does it that
means like we can have different
opinions we can fight and we can you
know but I just at the core of their
beings my parents are different people
and I just want to have some more
similarity than that but that's I don't
like they haven't like damaged me or
anything like that I've been divorced I
actually think they it's been great for
everyone in the family divorced the
hosta home
what is one sexual fantasy you would
like to have oh my gosh
just one
well definitely the airplane yeah thing
yeah I always want every time I'm on an
airplane
people are gonna steal two people go in
there oh yeah oh no oh and the flight
attendants yeah oh yeah
no no idea I don't know yeah that's a
very huge plane
yeah thanks Gare buses but uh let's
that's like too easy let me think of a
different way okay
[Music]
I don't know I just I think I think just
I guess just interesting places like I
like the letter that you wrote me which
is just all the places that we could
yeah I guess just different places what
would you change in me in you in reality
to make this work I was all sort of
myself sure I would change my skepticism
about it being able to work and I would
stop thinking so much it was like
thinking planning what's gonna happen is
and I think I would also change that in
you because I think you do that too and
I think it's like it could ultimately be
like a hindrance in continuing in
reality I would move the Bay Area down
just like Los Angeles I'm just like cut
it out I was flush lost actually I don't
make Los Angeles and put it up there
it's way better weather okay but that's
what I would do I would just put it in
the middle of the bay okay yeah and all
the San Franciscans would love that
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh it's ears that was mine so which of
my friends do you wish you didn't have
to hang out with and why I mean I've
never gotten much out of hanging out
with Keith my friend is not a friend
he's Dillon's boyfriend so doesn't okay
that doesn't count I don't even really
know him I just as many times as you
have yeah he's a nice guy he's a really
nice guy just don't we just spend
nothing I know don't blame conversations
yeah the super nice guy though yeah very
nice don't I both know that too um let's
see no I really think your friends are
really cool and I feel like I get along
fairly well with them yeah so my answer
it's like is like I I have no problem
with hanging out there cuz I think she's
really cool but I just don't know her
that well and my very limited impression
Sophie okay it's just very dramatic and
lots of talking and yeah and it's hard
for me to like keep up with like yeah
things but like I think she's very loved
like I mean I get excited like when
you're like oh so if he's coming over or
whatever you know like that's cool yeah
but I'd say like if I had to choose one
person to was it not have to hang out
with ya I'll answer it though you answer
it so I'll answer
I feel no that's not true
oh my gosh I'm just gonna start naming
your friends like in like say this out
loud I'm a bad I love you MA and look
who I love Michael I love Spencer I
think Cameron is like so scary but so
soft I'll just think about like you know
who I don't okay well I want to answer
it I don't know but I've been in
situations at parties with you where I
don't know anyone and I want to like try
to talk to people but I just oh you know
what
I you like made it so like you've really
built it up that I was gonna like have
this huge connection with Han Solo Hanna
oh and like I do I think she's really
great but I don't like feel as deeply
yes I think you did like you hoped or
something like she's awesome she is
awesome but we're just very different I
think it's the same thing is this for
you yeah sure very different but she's
cool how many people have you slept with
Wow yeah well this is actually the
question that I wrote down well I know
and I know I said it was evil yeah valid
yeah I wrote it because I was just
thinking like what is something that cuz
I was like I feel like we talk about
things a lot and like
I was trying to think of a moment when
we didn't like that that stood out that
like you know you didn't and I remember
that so I was like so I mean you don't
have to answer to but yeah it's just I
knew it was more than yours so I just
didn't want like it was so early when
you asked me that it was like we were
just getting to know each other and we
were like I don't know it was valid we
were like we had slept together so it
was a valid question like I think that's
okay to ask eight which I don't feel
like is a lot but I don't know I just
don't like I don't like to think about
that so I don't like this you know when
it's so unimportant to me I don't even
like that I know the number yeah even
like really care to know that much oh
that was the only thing that I could
think of okay it's eight including you
okay what is a secret that you have been
too afraid to tell me a secret
secretly I've been too afraid to tell
you
gosh I really don't know it's gotta be
something what do you do that's like
embarrassing you don't want me to know
oh all right sure but I've seen I pick
my boogers sometimes you know yeah I
feel like no people caught me made fun
actually
oh my god I wait I have to say something
really right what um when we were saying
in my mom's house oh my god this is
actually I've been wanting to tell you
this for so long yeah it was the
opportune moment okay you um I've got a
broom whoa wait I was in the bathroom oh
it's your sick kitchen no it's not no
it's all good I was in the bathroom
you're in the kitchen and there's this
window it was dark outside so the window
is like reflective and I was in the
mirror and I thought I had a booger so I
took like a tissue and I stuck it up my
nose and I was like moving it around in
there and then I look I just gaze over
in the reflection and you're doing the
exact same thing but you're just using
your finger but we were doing the exact
same thing and hiding from each other at
the exact oh wow I told like now all
your friends know I'm a booger picker
and they know what I am too I'll try to
think of something better a better
secret that I oh yeah yeah I think I'm a
better secret well I I can't think of
anything right now okay I don't think
there's anything like really important
that I haven't told you okay and
probably be very little okay but yeah
okay so I guess yeah
okay
what would make you leave me just like
okay we kind of talked about this before
but I was cheated on one time and I
didn't really care about the
relationship as like at the time it was
like going out it was on its way out and
I like it only affected me because of
the thought that I had like done
something that would warrant someone to
like look elsewhere like but I just
think like I don't know I don't it would
depend on what the situation was but I
just think there's no reason for it and
I mean that there should not be a reason
for it and if there is if you feel that
there is I don't want to be here anyway
like if you feel that you're not getting
something from me then I'm not this
isn't right anyway
because if we're having great sex if we
are you know we have a great connection
we can talk about whatever we want
there's just like why there's no reason
what so it'd be cheating I think so just
for lack of a better likes or if you
like hippier okay it's very reasonable
right
what do you see as the next steps in
this relationship the next steps um I
don't I think the next step in this
relationship is to leave here get a
drink
sneak little kisses like and cuddle yeah
are you scared I'll hurt you emotionally
yeah yeah I mean but yeah because I
really care about you and I think if
this if you were to tell me like
tomorrow that you don't ever want to see
me again like I honestly think I might
be pretty devastated like I am NOT ready
for that yet and just knowing that
something you know this could be over in
a matter of months depending on what
happens in our lives like that could be
really hurtful
but I I'm not afraid of it but yeah but
I know I am afraid of it but I wouldn't
let it stop me from like being you know
or like experiencing it the way that it
would be if there wasn't you know that
hanging around here
[Music]
tough question
what do you think is a weakness that I
have in this relationship
[Music]
think
I don't know I'm not a person that lets
go of things easily but I think that I'm
not a person like who moves on easily
but I am a person that like has been
because I've moved around like my entire
life I think I've maybe had practice and
I don't know I think that and I don't
really know how this is gonna sound I
just feel like if if we are kind of
forced to part ways then I think that
would be really hard for you and it
would be for me too
but I also feel like I have a tremendous
amount of love for just even just the
transience of of like a relationship you
can have with somebody and I think that
would help me in a lot of ways you had
to be honest like I'm really scared like
if we are if you do move up to the bay
or I like move away or something and we
have to and and like we have to break up
or however it ends up working I'm really
I'm really scared that it's gonna suck
really bad for you and and I wouldn't I
would never want you to be hurt you know
I know that I already knew that you have
to say it because I know like I know
that about you like I know how you just
like thrive on moving around and
traveling and learning and I love that
about you and I think I'm the same way
but I think if I find something good I'm
more likely to hold on to it and I don't
think you are because you know that
there's you know you know because you
know that there are other people that
you know and you know that and I know
that too for myself but I'm just I
wouldn't I probably wouldn't do the same
thing you would
because that's something that I don't
want you to be like I don't know how you
how I can say this and you know expected
of you I guess but I don't want you to
be afraid of hurting me it's kind of
inevitable maybe because of you know
things like feelings I have expressed to
you but I just like that's so not I just
want you to know that's not what I want
like I just want to have things be as
they are I think would be and I don't
want you to think about hurting me
because then you will and it'll be
earlier you know I just feel like
something will happen earlier than it's
supposed to because you're afraid and I
although I'm so afraid of like a lot of
things I'm not like I would never choose
not to move on with you because I'm
afraid of moving on with you
you know I would have I would have said
goodbye like a couple months ago I think
if that's how I was planning on being
I don't know it is what do you love
about me that I don't see with myself I
don't know if you don't see this but I
think you just so like you probably see
this are you like so spongy like you
just want to know everyone and you want
to like know everything and maybe you do
know that but I don't like it's just
like when we were a new year at that New
Year's party and you were all my friends
and you didn't know a single person
supper done really like you went over to
this group of people I don't even know
and you just wanted to know everything
about them and you were introducing me
to my friends acquaintances and like you
just you know I don't know if you
realize how like good you are at being
like I don't know open I guess I don't
know maybe you do I don't know I think
it's just kind of intuitive but ya know
I feel like I was looking like a really
shy person right yeah I thought oh you
just you ask everyone questions about
you want to know and you don't ask
questions that you don't really care to
know I think which is important to me
what do you love about me I don't know
you just there's I think it's a quality
that's very difficult to articulate but
I know within moments of meeting
somebody is and to me it's like the
highest compliment that you could give
somebody which is just like that you're
genuine do you know I feel like there
you meet so many people and there's all
of these walls and and and and not just
like being vulnerable emotionally but
just there's just a certain fakeness to
them and and I never felt that with you
and I feel like when everybody you meet
there's just a genuine just a genuine
interest in them and also just like a
genuine affection and thoughtfulness
towards them you know and I think that's
really special you know like I think I
think the best way actually probably the
best way to articulate is just to look
at your friends like the people that you
have around you are just like are all
amazing and the way that they speak
about you is not in a way that that is
you're a friend you know like they're
you know they're you're their family you
know like they would do anything for you
because they know that because they know
who you are and they know that you're
genuine and and you know that you would
do the same for them and I think yeah I
think that's something that's so hard to
find